GIIT Professional College is very
happy to introduce his student GURYASH
he's the student of BCA first semester
of 2018-21 batch and he has developed a
website which you will love to see so I
invite Guryash to come here and explain
his work.
Hi everyone I am a student of BCA
first semester of 2018-21 batch and GIIT
Professional college N-Road Bistupur. Firstly I would like to thank my college
for giving me skill development training
in web-based technology beyond syllabus. And I
am glad to say that I have designed one
website this consists of 32 pages 25
links 3 web application and more than 11
thousand lines of coding .Speaking about
the front end there is HTML, CSS and W3.CSS
and going to the back end there is
JavaScript jQuery AJAX PHP and MySQL- so let have a look over it. So this is the
homepage of my website it says world class
most experienced teacher so one of the
biggest trouble which comes in a student
life is getting good education and for
good education there should be better
tutors and that problem is solved by my
website INDITUTOR . So on going on to the
second slider we have --why so stress get
the best tutor nearby you .So this is the
another aspect of my way
which says why are you so stressed if
you can get best tutor nearby oh so you
need to travel a distance which is not
less than 11 miles - and so the problem is
solved by my website it searches for the nearby tutors according to your
location.
So let's go on to the next slide so it
says get in touch with the most trusted
tutors in your area. In our website the
tutors are not selected randomly, they are selected
according to a review system which is
one of application of my website. So all
of these three sliders working parts of
the student panel. So now let us go to the
another slider, it says join as a teacher
and get your business ready profile so
my website is not only for students but
it also have some favor for teacher so
if you are a teacher you can go to our
signup page select that you are a
teacher then you would be
taken to your profile menu where you can
upload your profile picture, your
description, your teaching arts and your
location and just your profile is ready
and yeah you are ready for a
professional future. So as we scroll down
my website it says how we work for you
so my website is a fully transparent
website. We work for the student so we are
totally transparent. Today. So what my
website does. It is we search for the
best tutor according to a requirement
the student enter its requirement and
in just a click all the tutors around
them are ready. Then you have a brief
counseling
not only that just work selected teacher
and you have to go to them you get a
brief counseling with them and three
to four our demo class after that after
that you were visited three to four
teachers you can select which one best
suits you so as we scroll down then
there are a list of our top tutors in my
review system the student rates the
teacher and according to the rating the
top six tutors are selected and
displayed in the homepage so these are
the tutor of chemistry physics
mathematics accounts computer and biology. And the next message says thousands of
tutor are getting new students with INDITUTOR sign up today for a better
tomorrow. So this message is basically to
attract teachers. Thousand of students are
connecting and teacher can connect to
acquire them. So as you scroll down there
is a student counter ,this is basically
a application which counts how many
students are connected with us; it is
good for teachers to take help of it .Then
getting help is easier than you think. Not we provide tutors, we're always there to
help you and that is discussed in this
section so let me talk something about
the menubar. Menubar consist of home button higher subject about us and phone numbers.
in the hire section you get a lot of
options :- home tutor, private tutor,
distant tutor, nearby, experience tutor and
study center. The most amazing part is
nearby tutor as I discussed earlier. As
you click on nearby tutor if first of all
its asks for your location so as you
click Next and allow your location,
then your latitude and longitude
locations are fetched and then thw
tutors around you are displayed and
fetch from our database and displayed
here. So basically this is a demo profile
which consists of teachers name his
subject his profile photo and a short
description and the ratings given by the
student so and if you want to write in
about a specific tutor you can just
a click and write a review and click on the submit button. So if the don't want to scroll by
teacher you can select subject box in this menu. So another section is aboutUs
section it says fortune favors the bold,
its message specifically for a purpose so as
we go down it says, we help you to be bold. We all know that education is what
which makes someone bold. So we provide you with better
educators so as you scroll down we see
about-Us section. Who are we it says who are
we are basically a large network of
tutors and students. Then how we work and
about our teachers how we earn. We are
hundred percent legal.Our work place and feel free to talk. We are always ready to help.
It is a website by student for the students. So there are always contact
numbers available over here. So this
was my website I hope you liked it. -Thank You.
okay a big clap